<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paper Note on Zhaoyu Li</title>
    <link>https://zhaoyu.li/tags/paper-note/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paper Note on Zhaoyu Li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Zhaoyu Li</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 04:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaoyu.li/tags/paper-note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper note - Loop Modeling</title>
      <link>https://zhaoyu.li/post/loop-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaoyu.li/post/loop-modeling/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents      Paper 1: [2000] - Modeling of loops in protein structures Paper 2: [2006] - A fold-recognition approach to loop modeling Paper 3: [2014] - Protein Loop Modeling Using a New Hybrid Energy Function and Its Application to Modeling in Inaccurate Structural Environments     This article is kind of a literature review of loop modeling but not complete.
Paper 1: [2000] - Modeling of loops in protein structures First (I think) paper about loop modeling is: Modeling of loops in protein structures (link).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper note - DenseNet</title>
      <link>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-densenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-densenet/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents      Brief Introduction Dense Connectivity Pooling Layers Growth Rate Bottleneck Layers Compression Memory-Efficient Implementation Implementation     There are two papers about DenseNet:
 Densely Connected Convolutional Networks Memory-Efficient Implementation of DenseNets  Brief Introduction In DenseNet, there are direct connections between any two layers with the same feature-map size. This introduces $\frac{L\times(L+1)}{2}$ connections in an $L$-Layer network, instead of just $L$.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper note - Accurate De Novo Prediction of Protein Contact Map by Ultra-Deep Learning Model</title>
      <link>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-accurate-de-novo-prediction-of-protein-contact-map-by-ultra-deep-learning-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-accurate-de-novo-prediction-of-protein-contact-map-by-ultra-deep-learning-model/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents      Contact definition Existing contact prediction methods Intuition Input features Network Structure Conversion of sequential features to pairwise features Loss function Regularization and optimization Proteins of different lengths Data Results Discussion     For contact prediction, direct evolutionary coupling analysis (DCA). However, DCA is effective on only some proteins with a very large number of sequence homologs. Paper link is here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper note - Globally and Locally Consistent Image Completion</title>
      <link>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-globally-and-locally-consistent-image-completion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaoyu.li/post/paper-note-globally-and-locally-consistent-image-completion/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents      Related Work Approach Training Hyperparameters     This is a (another) paper about image completion. It considers both the local continuity and the global composition of the scene, in a single framework for image completion. It also compares results with the previous methods.
Paper link: click me
Related Work Different approaches to image completion (inpaiting):
 Diffusion based Patch based Others  Comparison:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>